

CAGATAY DEMIRBAG JUNIOR .NET DEVELOPER

- linkedin.com/in/cagataydemirbag
- cagatayydemirbag@hotmail.com
- +905452535800
- https://cagatayyd.github.io/website
- https://github.com/cagatayyd

RELEVANT SKILLS

- JavaScript
- C#
- .NET
- SQL

LANGUAGES

• English C1

ABOUT ME

Hello! I am , 3rd-year student in Computer Engineering at Karabük University, and I have been developing myself as a web application and web API developer. Specifically, I have been enhancing my skills in MSSQL, C#, and .NET technologies. Throughout my university education, I have made intensive efforts to blend theoretical knowledge with practical experience. Participating in various projects has enabled me to enhance my problem-solving skills and sharpen my coding abilities. Thanks to my eagerness to learn and improve, I continuously update and refine my skills in these technologies. I enjoy working in a team and exploring new technologies. Keeping up with evolving industry standards and staying current in this field is important to me. I am adaptable to teamwork, possess advanced analytical thinking skills, and excel in problem-solving. My openness to innovation and change constantly propels me forward towards better software development

WORK EXPERIENCES

Supervisor

B2 Advertising Agency September 2019 to August 2021

Junior .NET Developer

The American Robert College of Istanbul December 2023 to March 2024

EDUCATION HISTORY

Department of Computer Engineering

Karabuk University August 2022 to Present

CERTIFICATIONS

The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp Cert f cate

Udemy

Modern Web Development Certificate Udemy

Beginner Frontend Web Development Path

patika.dev

Asp.Net Core Membership Systems

ASP.NET Core Web API Fundamentals pluralsight.com

REFERENCES

Hakan Kavalcı - Software Architect

The American Robert College of Istanbul https://www.linkedin.com/in/hakan-kavalci